const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"What is a complication of arsenic poisoning?","answers":[{"option":"Respiratory failure","bool":false},{"option":"Coma","bool":false},{"option":"Sepsis","bool":false},{"option":"Renal failure","bool":true},{"option":"Arrhythmia","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"A person fell from the second floor and landed on their feet. What is the injury seen in this case?","answers":[{"option":"Whiplash injury","bool":false},{"option":"Waddell's triad","bool":false},{"option":"Spinal shock","bool":true},{"option":"Skull fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Bird's feet injury","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"What is the main cardiovascular complication in chronic kidney disease patients with dialysis?","answers":[{"option":"Arrhythmia","bool":false},{"option":"Congestive heart failure","bool":true},{"option":"Myocardial infarction","bool":false},{"option":"Myocarditis","bool":false},{"option":"Valvular defects","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"Which of the following levels of spinal cord transection would lead to paralysis of all four limbs?","answers":[{"option":"T1-T2","bool":false},{"option":"C2-C3","bool":true},{"option":"T3-T4","bool":false},{"option":"T11-T12","bool":false},{"option":"C6-C7","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"Which of the following levels correspond to spinal cord transection leading to paralysis in only two limbs?","answers":[{"option":"T1-T2","bool":true},{"option":"C3-C4","bool":false},{"option":"S3-S4","bool":false},{"option":"C2-C3","bool":false},{"option":"C1-C2","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"Which of the following characteristics are suggestive of suicidal cutthroat?","answers":[{"option":"Carotid artery likely to be cut","bool":false},{"option":"Downsloping","bool":true},{"option":"No tailing","bool":false},{"option":"Upsloping","bool":false},{"option":"Commonly below the thyroid cartilage","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"Which part of the intestine is most commonly ruptured?","answers":[{"option":"Rectum","bool":false},{"option":"Duodenum","bool":false},{"option":"Jejunum","bool":true},{"option":"Transverse colon","bool":false},{"option":"Ileum","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"A person meets a road accident after which he loses continence and activity in his lower limb muscles for 2 days. Following this, both these symptoms resolve completely on their own. What is the likely etiology?","answers":[{"option":"Epidural hematoma","bool":false},{"option":"Obtundation","bool":false},{"option":"Spinal shock","bool":true},{"option":"Lumbosacral plexus injury","bool":false},{"option":"Coma","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"How many tablets of acetaminophen can cause poisoning?","answers":[{"option":"15","bool":false},{"option":"20","bool":true},{"option":"10","bool":false},{"option":"5","bool":false},{"option":"30","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"Which of these drugs can be used to prevent the recurrence of calcium stones?","answers":[{"option":"Furosemide","bool":false},{"option":"Allopurinol","bool":false},{"option":"Probenecid","bool":false},{"option":"Chlorthalidone","bool":true},{"option":"Ethacrynic acid","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"Which of these fractures is a sign of battered baby syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"Torus fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Pathological fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Greenstick fracture","bool":false},{"option":"Nobbing fracture","bool":true},{"option":"Spalding fracture","bool":false}]},{"id":11,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"Which of these drugs is not associated with hyperuricemia?","answers":[{"option":"Spironolactone","bool":true},{"option":"Hydrochlorothiazide","bool":false},{"option":"Niacin","bool":false},{"option":"Triamterene","bool":false},{"option":"Furosemide","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"Which of these organs can be ruptured by trauma to the epigastric region?","answers":[{"option":"Pancreas","bool":true},{"option":"Intestines","bool":false},{"option":"Spleen","bool":false},{"option":"Liver","bool":false},{"option":"Kidney","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"A crush injury during a vehicular accident most commonly ruptures which organ?","answers":[{"option":"Stomach","bool":false},{"option":"Kidney","bool":false},{"option":"Intestines","bool":false},{"option":"Liver","bool":false},{"option":"Spleen","bool":true}]},{"id":14,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"What is the most common causative organism for acute pyelonephritis?","answers":[{"option":"Escherichia coli","bool":true},{"option":"Proteus mirabilis","bool":false},{"option":"Enterobacter","bool":false},{"option":"Staphylococcus aureus","bool":false},{"option":"Pseudomonas aeroginosa","bool":false}]},{"id":15,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"A lesion at which vertebral level will cause paralysis of all 4 limbs?","answers":[{"option":"L1-L4","bool":false},{"option":"T10-T12","bool":false},{"option":"T4-T8","bool":false},{"option":"C4-C6","bool":true},{"option":"T12-L3","bool":false}]},{"id":16,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"A patient on dialysis for chronic kidney disease is likely to have what complication?","answers":[{"option":"Thromboemolism","bool":false},{"option":"Congestive heart failure","bool":true},{"option":"Neuropathy","bool":false},{"option":"Meconium ileus","bool":false},{"option":"Dementia","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"3rd-year/renal/2018","question":"What is the name of the organization for organ donation?","answers":[{"option":"World Health Organization (WHO)","bool":false},{"option":"United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO)","bool":false},{"option":"United organ donation organization","bool":false},{"option":"United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund (UNICEF)","bool":false},{"option":"United network for organ sharing","bool":true}]}]
export default arr